

# CHRIS LAWSON CAL POLY UNDERGRAD COMPUTER ENGINEERING



I am a Computer Engineering Cal Poly Undergrad and graduate of Atascadero High School where I was a programmer for our world-class robotics team. Before starting at Cal Poly, I was a Network Engineering Intern for a local ISP where I managed local servers and helped clients with technical support.





# Years of Experience Java Python Bash/Shell Git/GitHub Electronics CAD GCode



### **EDUCATION** -

### Cal Poly SLO, San Luis Obispo, CA

https://cpe.calpolv.edu/

#### 2020 - PRESENT

· Computer Engineering Major

### Atascadero High School, Atascadero, CA

http://ahs.atasusd.org/

#### 2016 - 2020

- · High-level, college prep classes
- Peer Mentoring class
- 5 on AP Computer Science Principles test
- · 3 on self-taught AP Computer Science A (Java) test
- Cuesta College Dual-Enrollment Video Production class
- · Cuesta College Dual-Enrollment Calculus class



### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Wilson Creek Communications - Network Engineering Intern

https://www.wilson-creek.net/

#### 2019 - 2020

- Access Point Maintenance
- Customer Technical Support/Installations
- · Backend Server Management

### FIRST Robotics Competition - Team 973, Atascadero High School - Programmer

https://www.greybots.com/

#### 2016 - 2020

- C++ Robot Code
- · Custom Web Python/JavaScript Robot Dashboard
- Custom Web JavaScript/Google Sheets/Firebase Time Clock System

#### **LifeGuard CPR and Aquatics, Atascadero -** Webmaster

https://lifeguardcpr.com/

### 2013 - PRESENT

· Implemented WordPress and commerce system for Safety Training Classes



## CERTIFICATE & AWARD -

- · 2x Letter in Academics
- Principal's Honor Roll
- The Randy and Sally Knight Youth Scholarship
- 2x AP Scholar